nutraplanet.com 2010-06-15

# Privacy Policy

At NutraPlanet, we recognize the importance of preserving and protecting your privacy. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our web site and our services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard your information.

To request a correction or deletion of your private information, or if you have any questions and general comments about this privacy policy, please contact us at [support@nutraplanet.com](mailto:support@nutraplanet.com)

**Contact Information**

NutraPlanet  
111 Bethea Rd Ste 101  
Fayetteville, GA 30214

phone: 770-460-1365

support email: [support@nutraplanet.com](mailto:support@nutraplanet.com)

**What Information Do We Collect?**

  * NutraPlanet collects personal information when you register for a service or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other services or third parties to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.
  * NutraPlanet uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our services in order to improve overall quality.
  * NutraPlanet servers automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request.

**Registration Information**

You will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you register to be a user of our services, register for certain services, or register for email newsletters and alerts.

**Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. If you use our "Email this page" feature to send a copy of that page to someone else, your email address will appear as the sender of the email. Both your email address and the recipient's email address will not be used for any other purpose.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Generally, we use personal information for purposes of managing and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable.

**Choice/Opt-out**

We allow you the choice to opt-out of having your information used for purposes not directly related to our site, when we ask for the information.

Until you explicitly opt-in for the first time we consider you in the opt-out category. We always notify our customers when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

If you do not wish to receive any promotional or marketing e-mails and/or surface mail marketing letters, you may opt-out of receiving those communications by using the opt-out mechanism on the User Account Settings Web page.

**What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

As you visit our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other customers. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security.

Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We may enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, and email for the purpose of providing you valuable products and services that we think will be of interest to you.

When we use third parties to assist us in processing and servicing our customers, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**

_Secure Information Transmissions_

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP. Please contact us if you have any questions or concerns.

**How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by contact us, see the above contact information.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. At any time you may request to view any and all changes and updates, via surface mail.

**Notification of Changes**

The Privacy Policy is subject to periodic review and change. In order to view the current Privacy Policy, simply check this section of the website.

| 

### Navigation

  * About Us
  * Ordering Information
  * Shipping & Returns
  * Customer Testimonials
  * Sponsored Athletes
  * Privacy
  * Conditions Of Use

---|---
